<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Blog Posts By Satish Tripathi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Blog Posts By Satish Tripathi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:57:47 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lambda Function Url</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/lambda-function-url/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:57:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/lambda-function-url/</guid>
      <description>What is function url? AWS Lambda Function URLs are unique HTTP endpoints that we can create using AWS Console, SDK or any other IaC tool. These URLs are used to trigger the Lambda function, and they can be integrated with a variety of workloads. Function URLs are dual stack-enabled, supporting IPv4 and IPv6. After setting up a function URL for the lambda function, it can be invoked through its HTTP(S) endpoint via a web browser, curl, Postman, or any HTTP client.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Your Infrastructure: A Guide to Upgrading Terraform state files from Version 0.12.31 to 1.3.6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/upgrade-terraform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/upgrade-terraform/</guid>
      <description>Why This Blog? The frustration of not finding a proper guide on the internet prompted the creation of this blog. Countless hours were spent researching, experimenting, and compiling the most effective and efficient upgrade process. We understand the importance of a smooth transition, and we&amp;rsquo;ve taken great care to ensure that every step is explained in a way that is easy to understand and follow.&#xA;Why it&amp;rsquo;s Important to Upgrade the Terraform version:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Spacelift GraphQL Query and Mutation Operations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/spacelift-graphql/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/spacelift-graphql/</guid>
      <description>About GraphQL:&#xA;GraphQL is a query language for your API and a server-side runtime for executing queries using a type system you define for your data. GraphQL isn&amp;rsquo;t tied to any specific database or storage engine and is instead backed by your existing code and data.&#xA;Types of Operation in GraphQL: Query - queries are used to fetch the data. Mutation- Mutations are used to modify server-side data.&#xA;Spacelift Graphql Query/Mutations: If your spacelift account name is deployment then your spacelift graphql endpoint would be:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
